



About Me

Hi! I'm Ali, a UX designer determined to aid organizations who support healthy communities, focus on social impact, and fuel grassroots change. My ten years of multidisciplinary experience in social impact projects, product development, and sustainable food systems informs my design practice. My human-centered and data-informed approach allows me to create highly impactful platforms for change.

UX Skills

Social Impact Design

Data Visualization

User Research

Information Architecture

Wireframing & Prototyping

Usability Testing

Frontend Development

Design Presentation

User Interfaces

Technical Skills

Figma

Adobe XD

UsabilityHub

DataDog

MetaBase

Visual Studio Code

Work Experience

2023-Present

Product Designer | AnkiHub

Flagstaff, AZ

Multidisciplinary team leader, strategically developing design strategies. Our social impact design agency partners with nonprofits, foundations, and education organizations that address pressing issues in the realm of environmental and social justice.

2019-2023

Co-Founder | Elicit Chocolates

Flagstaff, AZ

Co-created a web-based gourmet chocolate company, from branding, website design, user experience, marketing, and product development. Product focused on sustainability, social impact, and community

engagement.

2016-2020

Director of Community & Culture | Local Juicery

Flagstaff, AZ

Developed marketing and branding strategies both brick & mortar and online retail products. Led community engagement events and corporate wellness program. Contributed to menus, recipes, and website content.

2014-2015

Epidemiology Assistant | Pima Country Health Dept.

Tucson, AZ

Mapped public health data for county epidemiology programs using ArcGIS mapping software. Advised health department on data-driven improvements to disease-prevention programs.

Education

2024

UX Design Certificate & UI Specialization

CareerFoundry

2015

B.S. in Public Health & B.A. in English

University of Arizona, Tucson